Ahh.
Master Pain. what do we do?
Open the mouth.
The Chosen One!
Huh? What?
Baby...
Kill it!
We will all be cursed!
Hmm. Hmm?
Mm? Hmm!
Mm. lighter. mm-hmm.
So cute.
Bye-bye!
It's starting now.
The child had become a man.
Rolling to the bottom
of a gully.
he was raised
by various rodents.
Having no true home.
he wandered the wilderness...
in search of the one
who stole his life.
So on he walked...
and sometimes drove.
And occasionally.
partied with
the desert creatures.
Party! Party! Party!
Little did he know...
that before him lied
a mystical road...
of great warriors and legends.
Your days are over. mister.
He lived under constant attack.
What they had not accomplished
when he was a child...
they sought to now finish.
Through his adversity.
he learned to fight...
and fight well.
The more he fought.
the more his powers grew.
I mean. crap. man!
Look at that.
Ohh...
That's. like. his stomach plug
on the ground back there.
You don't see that every day.
I mean. that doesn't
really even seem possible
if you think about it.
with body organs and cartilage
and bones and...
I mean. I'm no doctor.
but it was like one clean chunk.
Uh-oh. Trouble.
Open your mouth!
Yi-yi-yi-yi-yi!
Yi-yi-yi-yi-yi! Uuh!
I need gopher-chuks.
Uh...
Uuh!
Our... sexual... preferences...
are... our... own...
business.
Yeah.
Oh. you.
Alfalfa.
Hey. oh. Huh?
He's an outsider.
Have you ever
seen him before?
Mm-mm.
Well. twice.
Hey. who's he?
I don't know.
And that day.
I vowed to find the man
who killed my family.
Can you help me?
And why have you come to me?
You are Master Tang.
Your skills are greatly known.
I've traveled many years
and miles to find you.
How many miles?
Would you say ten million?
Eh...
No. I don't think ten million.
Look. I need your help.
I live under constant attack.
Hmm. Your story
makes my heart heavy...
and my prostate weak.
My bladder is full to bursting.
I feel for you
and your grave loss.
However. it will be impossible
for us to help you.
Master. I implore you
to reconsider.
Hmm. Okay!
The man you seek.
his name is Master Pain.
He has great powers
and is well protected
by the Evil Council.
But now I am in a quandary.
For if your story is true.
then you would...
Huh?
What are the odds of that?
You would be the Chosen One.
Master!
Ah. again with
the squeaky shoes.
Master. I was hoping one day
I could be the Chosen One.
- Be quiet!
- Master!
I don't like him very much.
Let's kill him.
- Sit down!
- Eeyah!
I must apologize for Wimp Lo.
He is an idiot.
We have purposely
trained him wrong.
as a joke.
Hah!
If you've got an ass.
I'll kick it.
- Hmm.
- Legend tells us...
that the true Chosen One...
will bear the mark
of infinite wisdom.
Yea. yea!
What in God's name
is that thing?
He seems to be the reason
I'm pursued.
There are so many things
I've yet to understand.
- Does it have a name?
- Tonguey.
I should not have asked.
Still. this is a glorious day.
for the Chosen One
has come to free us
from the Evil Council.
I remember a long time ago...
when a good friend of mine
told me...
there would be a Chosen One.
There will be a Chosen One.
Then he told me...
of the significance.
It will be significant.
And then he killed the dog.
I now officially know too much.
And why are you in bed?
Oh. you won't even believe
what happened next.
- No. please!
- Very well. Chosen One.
I invite you to train with us...
until you find the whereabouts
of Master Pain.
- I'll do it!
- In your dreams!
Ohh...
Yes. yes.
Yes. play me like a drum.
By the way. my student Ling.
here. will assist you.
Be not concerned of her shyness.
for it will pass.
There you go.
I will stay...
eh. to train.
Thank you. Master Tang.
Now. you two.
on with your training.
Yes. Sure.
As you know.
I am a man of special needs.
You will now receive
the Fist of Fury.
Prepare the long rubber glove.
Eeny. meeny.
miney. moe.
I wonder where my glove will go.
Open your mouth!
Open it!
You! Open!
Hey. guys. what's goin' on?
Hey! Ooh!
Master Pain. it is a great honor
having you beating random people
in our town.
Especially that helpless man
you just hit. Welcome!
Hmm. My finger points.
Wimp Lo. you must be careful.
Your confidence
is disproportional
to your abilities.
You think losing is winning.
Heh?
Uh. uh... Huh?
Hmm. The Chosen One
is here to help us.
- I like him a lot. and...
- Listen! Shh.
I see the way you look at him.
I'm a man. too. you know.
I go pee-pee
standing up.
Hmm. Mm.
- I will defeat him!
- Please. don't.
I will...
defeat him!
Whee!
The Chosen One trained.
for part of him knew
what lied ahead.
Wow! I'll have some
of whatever he's smokin'!
Huh!
The others soon
warmed up to him...
and his "friend."
Mm! Mm. mm!
Hmm.
Knock. Knock. Who's there?
Your butt that's
about to be kicked.
Take a close look.
'cause I rule. baby!
And who do you rule?
The Large. Dark Nipple People?
I rock... and roll...
all day long. sweet Susie!
I challenge you!
Leap that wall
if you're so great.
Hmm!
Big deal.
Up and over! Oi!
- Hmm!
- Huh!
Now we'll...
learn who's the best.
Hmm!
Huh? I... Uh...
Aha! Face-to-foot style.
How'd you like it?
I'm sure on some planet
your style is quite impressive.
But your weak link is.
this is Earth.
Oh. yeah? Try my
nuts-to-your-fist style!
Oh! Uuh!
Who's laughing now?
Please. stop!
Wimp Lo sucks as a fighter!
A child could beat him!
I'm gonna count to three. and if
I hear one more friggin' squeak.
- I'm gonna take his shoes
and shove 'em up his...
- Chosen One!
Master Pain's in town!
Did you hear that?
Master Pain? Are you sure?
Gotcha now! Guy-ee!
Ay. ay!
Why? Why?
No! Please!
I am bleeding.
making me the victor.
Master Pain's meeting
with the mayor.
Oh. this is bad.
Eh. Master Pain...
will perform his skill.
Please.
Mm. hah!
Towel. Mm. thanks.
Now. then. Master Pain
has heard rumor...
that the Chosen One
was spotted in town.
Do what he says.
or he'll cut off
your big toe.
On that you can trust me.
Let him hear it.
Oh. that's tender.
That is tender.
Thank you.
I have been called "bad" before.
Many have said I do things...
that are not correct to do.
I don't believe in
such talk as this.
I am nice man
with happy feelings
all of the time!
First. a joke.
What do you get when you cross
an owl with a bungee cord?
- My ass.
- Nyah. ha ha! Ha ha!
- Enough!
- Hmph!
Gentlemen.
from this day forward...
you will all refer to me
by the name "Betty."
But isn't Betty a woman's name?
Easy. easy!
We don't want to lose
any more toes here.
You'll all have to excuse
Master Pain... uh. Betty.
It's 12:00
and time for his nap.
Heh. Betty?
Hmm. sleepy time.
Come along.
Whoo! Aah!
I must find if I. too.
possess this special skill.
Remember. do not stop
until I give you the signal.
or dramatically
throw you to the ground
and request a towel.
I'm ready.
Ooh. ow! You can't...
Could you please...
Er. uh. should we keep going?
He said to hit him until he gave
the signal to stop.
Did anyone hear the signal?
Well. he was whining
for a while.
Do you think whining
was the signal?
Rr-rr!
Hey. whoa. easy.
We should wait a second or so.
Hey. guys.
Come on. Oh. well.
Hey. wait. wait.
He did say the part about
dramatically throwing us
off his body.
Oh. that's right. Yeah.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Throw us off!
He's not gonna die. is he?
You think he wants his towel?
Hey. uh...
That's pretty still.
Maybe it's time we should...
We better get home. guys.
Nobody say anything to Mom.
Hmm?
Hmm.
Hah!
I am Whoa.
Okay.
It is not yet your time.
You must not stand against
Master Pain.
- It's "Betty" now.
- Oh. You must not stand
against Betty.
If you fight. he will kill you.
You need special training.
You cannot defeat him now.
- I'm-I'm sorry?
- You cannot defeat him now.
I will defeat him.
If you can beat him.
then you should have
no problem beating me.
Mm!
Ah! Hmm. not bad.
What's wrong?
The supreme gift.
Hmm?
You must trust
the power of the tongue.
Hmm?
But I must warn you...
In the meadow you will find
Betty's great protector.
Moon Yew.
Avoid the meadow.
We will meet again. Chosen One.
many more times...
in the sequel.
Ow!
Well. at least I have you. boy.
Master Tang.
what are you doing here?
I've come to kick ass.
Oh!
I know you seek the Chosen One.
And I know...
what you did
to his family.
Now... Ooh! Oi!
I'm going to beat you up!
Do you need a glass of water
or something?
Jeez. at least
cover your mouth!
- We're all going to catch it!
- Fight... or die!
Okay. I'll shake
your bouncy booty!
Hit it!
Please. Betty. Master Tang
is unable to fight you.
He's pretty sick.
Why. I oughta... Ooh!
Don't.
He'll kill you
like a small dog.
Let your anger be
as a monkey in a pinata.
hiding with the candy.
hoping the kids don't break
through with the stick.
Aw. jeez.
And now the snorting starts.
I'm sorry.
I must fight you
when I am stronger.
Good-bye. Sally.
It's Betty. you son of a pig.
The name is Betty.
But Chosen One.
I want to help you. but I...
I-I-I-I...
I... I just can't.
I won't. Whee-ooh!
He wasn't at the restaurant.
Do you know where he is?
No. no!
He'll kill you.
Don't go. Please.
Stay alive. Stay and live
a life here with me.
Ee-ooh-ee-ooh-ee!
Look. Ling. those curlicues
on your face make me so hot
I can't think straight.
He is well protected.
It's impossible.
You'll never make it.
Never make it.
Ever make it.
You'll never make it.
ever.
Don't you see?
You can't make it.
I implore you to reconsider.
Hmm. Okay.
He spends his time
at the top of a waterfall.
swinging a chain around.
There.
You've got what you wanted.
Now go!
Hmm.
Remember. avoid the meadow.
Huh?
Ahh!
Hmm! Hmm!
Whoa-oa-oa!
Hmm!
Hah! Huh?
Hah! Hah!
Mm?
Huh? You like it?
Huh? Feels good. huh?
Well. you must be
quite a fighter
to make it past my cow.
What is it you want?
Evil Betty.
I've come to finish something
I should've done years ago.
Remember these?
Well. you've grown.
I thought you looked familiar.
Sorry. I didn't recognize you
without crap in your pants.
I've trained my whole life
for this day.
I spanked you as a baby.
I'll spank you now. bitch!
- Good luck.
- Wait!
You mustn't!
You are not ready!
Who are you?
Ling's father.
Oh-ee-oh-ee-oh-ee!
Oh. dear.
No one man
can defeat Betty.
When you girls are done kissing.
I've got some ass kicking
for you!
I have to avenge my family!
Ohh!
At that moment.
the Chosen One learned
a valuable lesson
about iron claws.
They hurt like crap. man!
Chosen One! Oh!
Shirt ripper!
Chosen One was
clearly not ready.
He should have listened
to that one-boobed chick.
Hmm!
Water... everywhere!
Uuh! All over me!
I'm... getting... wet!
Uuh! I'm falling!
You're falling!
We're falling!
A whale!
Mm-mm. Hmm.
Mmm. memento!
Huuh. Chosen One. I am sorry.
I'll get you some help.
Let me know if you see
a Radio Shack.
Hmm.
- Once again.
- With feeling.
One... of us...
is wearing... a pushup bra.
It's lacy...
Master Tang. please help me.
- I'm bleeding.
- Hey! I remember you!
Just like old times!
Ah. Rikki-Tikki-Tavi!
Rikki-Tikki!
Too tight! Stop hugging me!
I have a mortal wound!
Where?
Where does it hurt?
Oh. pretty much around
the big. bloody spot. Oh!
Come inside.
I'll get the Neosporin.
Please. I'm dying.
You must listen to me.
I feel the Chosen One
may give up hope.
This must not happen.
The creature in his tongue.
although a little disturbing.
possess a great
supernatural power-r-r!
W-Without Tonguey.
the council is invincible.
They will come to Betty's aid.
Do you understand?
No.
I don't understand you.
- Aha!
- No. Don't do that. It hurts.
No. it's good. it's good!
No. no. please.
I have a wound there.
Come on.
Don't spoil everything.
This works for both of us. huh?
Yeah-ahh!
The news of your father
weighs heavy on my heart.
Evidently. his wound
never closed up properly.
He gave his life for mine.
I'm so sorry. Ling.
He was my father my entire life.
We were friends.
I loved him.
And now he's dead...
except for his hair
and nails... dead.
I don't understand...
why people have to die.
Whee-ooh-whee-ooh-whee-ooh!
And now...
if-if I lose you...
Oh. man. I'm a little.
tiny. horny honey.
Mm.
- Hmm!
- Mmm!
- Mm-mm-mm!
Ooh-whee-ooh!
Oh. but I don't know.
It's so soon.
I can't remember the last time
I felt like this.
So ready for action.
So ready for love!
Hmm?
I need you now in the worst way.
I can't control it!
Take me. man meat!
But I don't want you
to think I'm a slut.
Huh?
What? What now?
How do I proceed?
Simba.
I... am not Simba.
I am the Chosen One.
Ah. yes.
I am Mu Shu Fasa.
You must not be troubled.
Cho-Simba One.
He took everything from me...
a family I never knew.
What good am I now?
His powers are greater
than mine.
Yes. plus when you were
hit with his iron claw.
you did scream like a wussy.
Look inside yourself.
Cho-Simba.
You must take your place
in the great circle of...
stuff.
Behold the symbols.
One over here.
the other over there.
Remember. weakening
and defeating Betty...
is the first step
to revealing
the council's identity.
What is this Evil Council
everyone speaks of?
The answer you seek resides
in the stars above.
I don't understand.
Of course you don't.
I'm speaking in riddles.
That's kind of the point.
like a clue that will
later make you go.
"Oh. that's what he meant!
Stars above!"
Please tell me.
What is my purpose?
Train. Cho-Simba.
You must reach the next level.
This is CNN.
Wait. Mu Shu.
CNN.
What of my tongue?
C... N...
Mu Shu!
N!
Hmm? A tiger.
Hmm?
Tiger. tiger. tiger.
Hmm! Bird.
Birdie.
Birdie. birdie.
Hmm.
I am a great magician.
Your clothes are red!
Wow! Please.
- Do it again.
- Wait. who's that?
B... Betty.
H-He's alive.
Betty.
He's still alive. Betty.
Still alive!
How can that be?
Oh. this is bad.
This is very bad.
Your clothes are black.
Oh. the council
will not be pleased.
Uh. but. Betty.
do they have to know?
He's supposed to be dead.
I am responsible.
Nyah!
He. alone. can disrupt
the Evil Council's plan.
Him and that
infernal Tonguey!
Eh. red clothes!
Uh. Master Betty.
might I inquire. what is
the Evil Council's plan?
Huh! It is evil.
My. it is so evil!
It is a bad. bad plan...
that will hurt many people...
that are good.
I think it's great.
'cause it's so bad.
I-I see...
I think.
But. Master Betty.
what of the Chosen One?
Hmm.
I'll kill him.
I'll kill him dead.
Hmm. like with...
with a rock or something.
Like a... like a stone.
He carries the basket.
He carries the paper roller.
Yaah! Hmm.
Have you seen him before?
Never!
Ventriloquists. huh?
Nyah. nyah. nyah!
You know the location
of the Chosen One.
Where is he?
On the life of my dummy.
I swear this...
I'll never tell you
where he is!
I am the Chosen One.
outside the wall!
Yeah. the wall!
Your mouth tricks
will not work on me.
ventriloquists.
And so began
Betty's killing spree.
No one was safe.
Ouchie!
Aiding the Chosen One...
became an offense
punishable by death.
Hmm. Orson.
Welles.
I swing a bit more.
I swing a bit less.
Got ya.
Whee-oh!
What? Please!
Hold still. ma'am.
Here she is. Betty.
The Chosen One disappeared
last night.
- What have you
done with him?
- Funny.
I thought you could tell me.
Hmm. In your dreams.
Whee-oh!
Hmm!
I like 'em feisty.
You disgust me.
Whee-oh-oh-oh!
Ee-oh. whee-oh. pee-oh.
ee-oh. pee-oh!
Whee!
Whee! Ohh!
She hit me. Betty.
No!
Go follow her. then save her...
for me.
Coo-coo!
I'm just a birdy too.
Uh-huh? Uh-huh?
- Huh?
- Yaah!
Okay. so here were my options.
"A." quickly duck sideways.
dodge the claw.
then take him out
with a spinning back kick.
Or "B." take the claw
in the face.
then roll on the ground and die.
Hmm. Should have gone
with "A."
That's right!
Follow me!
Right into my trap!
You go that way.
I'll go home.
Hmm? Hmm?
Huh?
Hmm?
Oh! Chosen One!
Ling?
Hurry!
- I'm coming!
- Chosen One!
I'm coming!
Chosen One!
Go get some snacks.
Perhaps a carbonated soda.
I hope they have Icees!
I've chosen the large tub.
My nipples look like Milk Duds.
I've got some yellow liquid
for your popcorn.
and it's non-dairy.
I... will... not...
be stopped...
by a tiny net!
I'll reverse the capture method.
and yaah... free.
Now I have to find Ling.
Ling!
Wimp Lo?
Chosen One.
Huh? Master!
- Chosen One.
- Oh. Master.
Do I look all right?
Uh. yeah. sure.
O-On a scale
from one to ten...
Uh... one.
Come.
C-Come closer. please.
Listen and listen well.
I really like the band 'N Sync.
My favorite member is Harpo.
I think there's a Harpo.
If not. there should be.
I will write
their next hit. maybe.
By the way.
you must be wary
of Betty's iron claws.
They are sharp. and they hurt.
And beware his song
about big butts.
He beats you up
while he plays it!
Master. no!
Chosen.
Huh?
Ling!
Chosen One.
I'm... dying.
No. Please.
Remember.
I will always...
love... you.
Whee! Ee-ee!
Ling! Ohh!
Huh?
Dog!
Oh. it's okay. boy.
- No. it's not. Huh?
- Chosen One.
Master!
Oh. Master.
You're alive.
I only did this...
That doesn't mean
a person is dead.
Chosen.
Huh?
Ling!
Chosen One.
Why did you run off?
Why did you leave me?
- But I thought...
- Huh?
Oh. dog! You're alive!
Hey. if you're all alive.
then surely Wimp Lo...
Wimp!
Oh.
Betty has gone too far.
Killing is wrong...
and bad.
There should be a new.
stronger word for killing...
like "badwrong"
or "badong."
Yes. killing is "badong."
From this moment.
I will stand for
the opposite of killing.
"gnodab."
Excuse me. kind blacksmith.
Do you know where I can find
little. silver. triangular
pyramid caps...
- roughly an inch
and a half in diameter?
- Right here in my hand.
Yaah!
Betty's protective caps
were the source of his power.
In order to defeat him.
they would have to be removed.
Chosen One tried and tried.
but they were
too smooth to pull
and pointy.
So they would. like.
poke your hands...
if you didn't get it
just right.
So he got frustrated.
as any one of us would.
Okay. maybe a little more
than any one of us would.
I'll never be able
to do it. ever!
Don't look at me!
Your hands... let me see.
It hurts?
How 'bout now?
And now?
And this?
You broke a thermometer
in my hands.
Rub it all in my hair.
You just get stranger
and stranger and stranger.
Your hands...
How are they now?
I don't know.
They feel like
they're on fire.
Huh.
So you really think that's hot?
'Cause I'll show you hot.
Now try.
You have helped me reach
the next level.
And here I was starting
to think you were just
a sadistic psycho bitch.
So. what you...
what you guys doing
later. huh?
I was just going
to hang out. but...
maybe we could get a pizza
or. you know.
scam some chicks
or something. right?
'Cause. um. I don't know...
I do like the ladies.
you know. I do like 'em.
Hmm. I like-a them.
and they like-a me back.
Master Betty. my compliments.
That tiny net was surefire.
Hmm. yes. a tiny net
is a death sentence.
It's a net. and it's tiny.
Sure.
At this very moment.
he's out in a field.
rotting like a papaya.
while we're in here.
cozy and enjoying
the good life.
Huh?
Oh?
Oh. man!
This is all I need.
Hmm. Hmm.
Uh. E-Evil Council?
I-I. uh.
got-got your message.
Hello?
N-Now batting.
Mike Piazza!
Whoa. Oh. s-sorry.
Evil Council.
I-It's just echoey.
and I...
No. that-that
is not possible.
Not again.
He has to be dead.
No. no.
I can handle him.
but. of course.
welcome your assistance.
So he's at the temple.
Thank you. Evil Council.
This guy is toast.
Tell me...
what you're thinking.
Of how best to deal with Betty.
But you've mastered
your technique.
You should be able
to beat him now.
I'm sorry?
But you mastered your technique.
You should be able
to beat him now.
I got everything
but the last part.
through "you should be able."
You should be able
to beat him now.
Perhaps. but wooden dummies
don't fight back.
While I'm ripping out the caps.
I'm completely defenseless.
For instance.
the first move
could be like this.
I could leap like a freak.
then throw in a back-snapping
eel strike.
But he'd have
a clear shot at my ribs.
I could always pretend
I'm a bird.
But that would just look stupid
and leave my small. sensitive
balls completely exposed.
The best approach would be
to go for both caps at once.
No matter what the tactic.
they all have a flaw.
You should be able
to beat him now!
No matter.
I think I have an idea.
We're children!
- I'll take a pound of nuts.
- That's a lot of nuts!
That'll be four bucks. baby!
You want fries with that?
He just left with nuts!
I know you're here.
My name's Betty.
Nyah!
Huh?
Yaah!
Waah!
Shirt ripper!
Hit it.
Hmm. I could dance like that...
if I felt like it.
You killed my family.
and I don't like
that kind of thing.
Eh? Oh. doggie hump.
And then all hell broke loose.
Oh. yes. the council.
Ho-ho!
Yes. the Evil Council...
are aliens.
They're French.
Ha-ha-ha!
Stinky pits and all. baby!
Okay. fire me up.
Oh. yes!
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha!
Oh. God.
Hmm. as you've
probably concluded.
the Evil Council
is based in France...
and will soon rise
to world domination.
Enjoy the paralyzer!
Huh?
Another paralyzer!
Say good night. floppy.
Hmm.
Your booties.
Do it for your family.
and so I can be in the sequel.
Stars above. Aliens.
Was I right or what?
Oh. you need to open your mouth.
Sacrebleu!
Uh... Huh?
Oh. no. guys. Come on!
Ouch. I fell
and hurt my tummy.
Thank you. squirrel friend.
Your soft. cushy body
helped absorb the force
of his blow.
Now. for my part of the bargain.
Chosen One!
Chosen!
Whee! Whee! Whee!
Chosen. you're alive.
It's okay. Ling.
There's nothing to
worry about anymore.
That's what he thought.
What is your purpose?
Whee-ohh!
Hmm. I see you brought
your friends this time.
You mustn't.
You are not ready.
Rub it all in my hair.
Let me know if you see
a Radio Shack.
He has great powers
and is well protected
by the Evil Council.
He has great powers
and is well protected
by the Evil Council.
And playback.
That's a lot of nuts!
That... Why don't you
turn it down a little bit?
Open your mouth.
Yea-yea!
Okay. cut.
I-I can't work
with this thing.
Yea-yea!
At least the winking...
the winking has to stop.
Stop the...
Yea-yea!
Look. I'll get some tweezers...
and choke you
with a cotton ball.
you son of a...
Okay. I'm gonna
need a cup.
Up and over!
And now he's dead.
Oh. jeez.
I forgot my line again.
I think it's...
Oh. thank you.
Oh.
You don't seem
too sweaty...
No. don't do that.
It hurts.
Cut! Cut!
The director said cut.
You should stop that now.
Yeah. I'm aware of that.
I'm rehearsing.
You know...
Rehearse.
From this day forward.
you will all refer to me
by the game...
Oh. jeez.
Did I say "game"?
It was a long day.
Hey. is someone
going to come get me?
There's like a hawk
or something.
Oh. dear.
That's not good.
Um. Mr. Hawk.
could you please. uh.
stop with the leg-eating?
Oh. my.
Hey. it's not funny.
What's so...
He's a predator.
for crying out loud!